3/19/23, 7:16 PM Shivam Ratlam

Shivam Ratlam

Frontend Developer Mumbai, India

shivamrat.dev

ratlamwala

₩ shivam

Tools and Tech Skills

Photoshop, Final Cut Pro, Figma, Webflow, Sketch, Illustrator

Industry Knowledge

Javascript, CSS, HTML, MongoDB, React, Tailwind

Languages

Gujarati(Native), English

Education

Web Design and Programming

TSEC

2022 - Now

Computer Programming

St Lawrence 2017 **-** 2019

About Me



After graduating from the programming department, I worked remotely on graphic design for about 5 years. I have been working to be a

Front End Developer for the last 7 months and I am looking for a job in this field. Because of my old job, *I give importance to design and visuality in my work*.

EXPERIENCE

Graphic Designer, Data Analysis

JPMC | 2016 - 2020

My job task: Preparation of up-to-date statistics according to the situation in the stock market. Preparing visual infographics about the obtained data and organizing these data..

Senior Analyst

Amazon | 2021 - Present

My job task: Leading a team of 5 colleagues, selcting and shortlisting statistics and infographics, analyzing data and presenting data weekly...

PROJECTS

CV Builder ☑

With this project you can create real time CV. You can see the changes you have made live. Built with Tailwind and contextAPI.

shivamrat.dev

My personal website, that I created with Next.js, Tailwind Css, Content Layer.

Weather App 2

In this work, a small project where I visualize the data from the API.